aworkoutroutine.com 2019-04-01

# AWorkoutRoutine.com Privacy Policy

What’s up? Welcome to my privacy policy.

Everything you see below was compiled to help you better understand how your personal information is handled when using this website.

Since your privacy is _extra_ important to me, I’m going to be quite a bit more detailed and transparent here than you’re probably used to seeing on these types of pages.

If you don’t feel like reading it all (I don’t blame you, I was bored to death just putting it together), I can sum it all up by saying the following…

  * I only ask for and collect information about you when there is a legitimate need for doing so. For example, if you fill out a signup form to get one of my free workouts, I’m going to ask for/collect your email address so I know where to send it. _Duh_.
  * Other data I collect is for similar commonsense purposes, all of which involve some aspect of providing you with the products, services or content you requested, communicating with you, improving this website in some way, or something similar.
  * I don’t store any of your personal information for any longer than I have a logical reason or need for doing so.
  * I NEVER sell any of your information. At all. To anyone. For anything. Ever.

That was the short version. The longer, more thorough and more official version is below. If you have any questions about anything you see, you can contact me [here](https://www.aworkoutroutine.com/contact/).

#### Your Consent

By using this website, you consent to this privacy policy.
